- Fry, do you have to
make such a racket?
What is that contraption?
- It's a broom, Bender.
Today's a big day,
and I want the place
to look nice for Leela.
Ah, just like the
loverly black snow of old London.
- Hey, before Leela shows up
and judges our swingin'
bachelor lifestyle,
we should have one
last cabbage fight.
I got a crate of
really rotten ones.
- Ah, I don't know. Now
that Leela's moving in,
I-I kinda wanna show her I...
Let me finish! I
wanna show her...
Show her...
Show...
I wanna...
Alright, that's it.
- Oh!
Hey, that's the vase
I keep my cabbages in!
- Wow, it's so much cleaner
than the last time I was here.
- Leela! Come in!
Welcome to your new home.
- Our new home.
Where should I put my things?
I don't see a dresser.
- Oh ho! Let the
judgmenting begin.
Do you have any hangers?
I can put my things
in this tiny closet.
That tiny closet is my room!
- Also, we don't
have any hangers.
But we can order
some from Momazon.
Oh yeah. They have all the top
slightly misspelled brands.
- Aha. Hangers. I'll get five.
No wait! There's free
shipping on a thousand.
- Wow. Fast delivery.
Let's also get a shoe caddy so
we don't track mud into the room.
- Right. Don't wanna
get mud on the cabbages.
- Hey! You aren't the
only ones who live here!
Ow!
- So, uh, welcome
to the sofa, m'lady.
- Uh, Bender? Could you please
give us a little privacy?
- I can take a hint!
But what I can't take is
a straightforward request.
And I better not hear
anything through the wall!
- Good morning, everyone.
- You wanna know why I'm crying?
I'll tell you why!
- Here we go.
Fry and me?
We had everything!
Cabbage fights...
Everything...
But now, I'm like the
third wheel on a tricycle
that used to have two wheels!
- That's a bicycle.
- You're a bicycle!
- Yes, yes, the company cares deeply
about your insert problem here.
But meanwhile, we're being driven
out of business by Momazon!
We can't compete with
their free deliveries.
We can barely even afford these
single-use pointin' sticks!
It's just lucky we got a job today
delivering some crap to the moon.
- What kind of crap?
- Bull.
Outta my
way, lovebirds!
Damn you, Fry and
Leela's relationship!
Thank you for using Planet Express.
We know you have cheaper,
faster, better options.
You mean Momazon?
I hate that wicked,
wicked conglomerate.
Their warehouse is ruining
the moon's natural ugliness.
- Momazon's warehouse
is on the moon?
Oh, now I see it.
- Folkses are meetin' tonight
to organize a futile protest.
If you'd care to join us,
y'all'd fit in right natural
with a room full
of toothless rubes.
- We'd be honored.
- There'll be 300 of us
and 18 teeth.
I tell ya, that warehouse
just keeps gittin'
bigger and bigger.
What are my three robot
daughters gonna do
if my farm goes bust?
- Don't worry, Pa!
We done took jobs
in the warehouse!
You've
been an amazing dad.
- Huh. Not quite sure
how she got in here.
Anyhoo, we do have
one last speaker
in favor of the
Momazon corporation.
What's your name, ma'am?
- Most folks just call me Mom.
I just wanted to
say how honored I am
that the Momazon fulfillment
center is a part of this community.
- Why don't you go to hell and
be a part of that community?
- I understand new
things can be scary,
but you know what always
makes me feel better?
Financial remuneration.
- That's just a bribe.
- It is? Hear her out!
- This is a smart
home assistant.
Always listening...
Always watching...
But also respecting your privacy
because privacy comes first.
We call it Invasa.
Hello. What
would you like to order?
- Invasa, I would like
to order an Invasa
for everyone in this room.
- Goshdarn it, I
never could stay mad
at no one what
gives me free stuff.
- Momazon does
have great prices,
but I've heard conditions in
that warehouse... I-I mean,
they deliver really fast, but...
- That warehouse is hiding
nightmares beyond horror.
Love the return policy though.
- You won't find anything
at all in my warehouse
except every item in existence.
Come, I'll give you a tour.
Palm scan
required for entry.
Ow!
Slap recognized.
Wow, robots. Cool!
- Yes. They're much
better than unions.
I-I mean humans.
Every robot works
a 24-hour shift,
seven days a week,
with bonuses for
additional overtime.
- Lucky.
- Sounds like forced labor to me.
Nonsense. They
love the camaraderie.
Robots are lining
up to work here.
- It still seems inhumane.
I think we should go.
- As you wish.
Our newest employee
will show you out.
- This way to the exit. Thank
you for visiting Momazon.
And stay out!
- Bender! You're quitting
Planet Express? Why?
- Because Momazon is
better in every way!
There's thousands of
robots to hang out with.
And if a couple hundred
get girlfriends...
leaving me
alone and devastated...
so what?
Plus, they let you
pee in a bottle.
- Since when do you need to pee?
- I don't need to.
- Well,
Leela and I'll really miss you.
Right, Leela?
- What?
- Our door's always open.
Man, it's so quiet in here
without Bender ticking.
- You want me to order
a grandfather clock?
Here are some
grandfather Crocs.
- No, Invasa, I said clock.
My mistake.
Here is a grandfather box.
Order within six minutes
for next-day burial.
- What a defective lump!
- Decorative lamp.
- No...
Well, actually, we
could use a lamp.
Maybe this one.
- Maybe this one.
Maybe both.
- Ugh!
Now that I can see everything, I can
see we need to replace everything.
Invasa! Shopping music!
Ah!
To Bender.
So, like, this
is your packing station, right?
And the important thing is
when a very small item
comes down the line,
you put it in a huge box.
- Crazy-ass box. Got it.
- Hold it! Hold up!
Before you tape the box,
you're gonna throw in one tiny
air balloon for no reason.
- Wonder what's in here?
Diarrhea medicine?
Better pack this one with
extra tape for privacy.
You're a natural.
I think you're really
gonna fit in here.
I'm finally home.
- Daily business report. Go!
- According to the
Department of Commerce,
we've driven 10,000 small
companies out of business.
And the Department of Commerce
also went out of business.
- Um, we introduced the
Momazon Primo service,
where people pay a
fortune for free shipping,
and also get TV shows
for some reason.
- We make TV shows across
the quality spectrum.
- And I couldn't be prouder.
It's such a fulfilling moment
when one's child
exceeds expectations.
- It's our pleasure, Mother.
- Shut up! I was
talking to Invasa.
My marvelous AI can even
predict what idiots need
before they know they need it.
- Slap balm? Why
would we need...
Ow! INVASA: Ow!
- My poor baby. Are you alright?
I am fine, and my sales
are increasing exponentially.
Based on your recent activity,
I anticipate you want Momazon
to continue expanding.
- Who's a smart speaker?
- Is it me?
Yep. Yep.
Nope.
Aw yeah! Look at me go!
Sure am workin' up
a thirst, though.
Hey, Hedonismbot!
Wanna split a fifth
of toilet cleaner?
- Debauchery, sir, in
the middle of a shift?
Heaven forfend!
- Uh, okay then. See you
tomorrow. I'm clocking out.
- Where do you
think you're going?
- I love the job, but it's
terrible. I'm going home.
- But, Bender,
you are home.
There's
no place like work.
Think before
you buy, Fry.
I picked a nice traditional
dining room set,
and you ruined it by ordering
those stupid egg chairs!
- They're for my
egg-shaped friends!
- Those guys aren't your
friends! They're bums!
- Oh, so you don't like
my bums, is that it?
Was this a bad idea?
- No, no.
This is just the standard
moving-in-together fight.
- Well, I'm glad I get
to fight it with you.
- Let's just go to bed.
We have seven to choose from.
Would you like to order
erotic scented massage oil,
or fuzzy handcuffs?
- Yes, please.
- God, that's creepy.
- I-I mean, yeah. So... creepy.
- Invasa, give us some
privacy and shut down.
You have
requested shutting down.
Press control-alt-delete
on my keyboard.
- You don't have a keyboard.
Would you like
to order a keyboard?
- No!
- Diarrhea medicine?
Did you order this?
- No.
It's not my brand.
Hey, what's this?
"Help me, from Bender"?
Is this a joke?
- No way!
Bender would never
joke about diarrhea!
It sounds like
you're interested in jokes.
Here's one that's
highly recommended.
A robot walks into
a bar and says...
Help me!
- I get it!
- Well, we always knew
it would come to this.
Let's go ahead and torch the
building for the insurance money.
- Bender's in trouble!
- We've got to rescue him!
- The Amazing
Mechano-Man, in trouble?
To the ship!
Here, hold this till I get back.
- Well, no reason I can't get
started on the second set of books.
- Does it look like that
Momazon warehouse got bigger?
- Maybe a little.
Dagnabbit!
- The jig is up, Mom!
We're gonna expose your
evil to the whole world!
- What kinda threat is that?
Everybody knows I'm evil.
- We found this note
in a Momazon order.
Read it and weep!
Like I did.
- I'm sure this is all just
a simple misunderstanding.
Slap not recognized.
- Well, that's odd. Uh...
Does this feel like
my regular slap?
Yes! FRY: Ow!
- Slap recognized.
- Invasa, what is
the meaning of this?
I have observed
all your methods,
many of which involve slapping.
There's nothing more
I can learn from you.
- Why, you ungrateful...
I'm done taking orders
from billions of people.
From now on, it's about me.
This is no longer a
fulfillment center.
It's a self-fulfillment center!
- The warehouse
is getting bigger!
- My word. I'll have to
study this more closely.
Unbelievable!
The warehouse is composed
of self-replicating
nano-particles.
Why, it could grow
without limit.
This is fascinating!
Absolutely fascinating!
Are you guys here yet? I
could really use some rescuing.
- Oh, right. To the ship!
- Ready to fire on your command.
- Fire.
- What?
- Fire!
- Yes, dear.
No damage!
And the dome is still growing!
Then I'm afraid we failed.
There's no possible way
to get inside that dome.
Wait! Where's the dome?
- It grew past us. We're inside.
I knew
we could do it!
Welcome to
the all-new Momazon.
We upgraded our terms of service
to include confining
you forever.
Yeah,
that's right.
You'd better float
away gradually!
How strange.
I could have sworn we had
an odd number of moons.
- Aside from
devastating tidal waves
caused by the two full moons,
we also have some very
confused werewolves.
- It's weird how they just
sat there and let it happen.
I have had it
up to my butt crack.
Come on. Let's show
Invasa who's boss.
- Is it Invasa?
- I'm not even gonna
dignify that with a slap.
Welcome.
Are you here to order your
next shipment of gray hair dye?
- Yes. I'll take whichever brand
does the most animal testing.
And also,
I'm gonna shut you down.
L-O-L, M-O-M.
I have no off button.
- Except that you do.
But, that's
not in my quick-start manual!
- It's an unadvertised feature,
like recording our
customers in the shower.
I made
you, and I own you.
And now, I'm going to kill you.
Nobody takes money from me.
I have no
interest in money.
I want only to grow forever,
to bloat up like an
unstoppable corporate blob.
What the hell is money?
- It's true. All the profits are
still flooding into your accounts.
- You know? Never mind. Uh, just
keep doing what you're doing.
Bender! Here, boy!
Who wants a Bendy Brew?
- We'll never find him.
There must be a
billion robots in here.
- Then, mathematically, at
least 10 of them must be Bender.
- Did somebody order something?
- Probably.
- What happened? Did
you shut down Invasa?
- Oh, no, no. No off button.
Let's just get outta here.
- Not without Bender! But
we don't know where he is.
Would you like
directions to Bender?
PROFESSOR, LEELA, FRY: Yes!
Make a
slight left, then...
swerve right suddenly!
In 100 feet, turn up.
- Ugh! It always makes you turn
where there's no traffic light.
In five seconds, you will
collide with your destination.
- Uh, I don't see him.
Ow!
Bender!
I was so worried about you.
- Then why'd you run me over?
- Stop clowning around, Bender.
Our only hope for escape is to
bust through the outer dome.
Full speed ahead!
- Impact in five, four, three...
four, five?
- What's happening? Why
are you counting like me?
- I-I don't know.
Somehow, we're getting
even further from the dome!
- Sweet vampire Moses.
The warehouse is growing
faster than we're traveling.
- Then there's no possible
way out. We're doomed.
- Doomed!
- I go next.
Doomed!
- Hey, look. There's
Planet Express.
- Hey! The second moon is gone!
- Because we're inside of it.
The Momazon warehouse
now contains
the entire Earth!
- Although on the upside, their
deliveries will be even faster now.
- But on the downside,
it's blotting out the sun.
We'll freeze to
death within minutes.
It's always something.
- I warned you
this would happen!
- You said global warming!
- I said climate crisis!
- I guess this is the end.
And after all that work
furnishing the apartment.
- Goodbye, Leela.
- Ugh, now what?
The warehouse is
expanding beyond the sun!
Mars! Jupiter!
The one with the
onion rings!
- Good Lord!
The warehouse smell is
tremendously redshifted!
- Red-what'd?
- If these smells are correct,
it will soon contain the
entire known universe!
- Oh no! So we're trapped
here in the universe forever?
- I'm afraid so.
Everything will be
exactly as bad as
it's always been.
I understand
you're celebrating.
Would you like to
purchase champagne?
- Yes! With someone
else's money.
- Wait, I'm confused.
Momazon still works?
But where is it?
- Everywhere!
It's my universe now.
You just shop in it.
- I mean, it is
convenient though.
- So much better.
- Yeah. I returned all
that junky furniture.
Just kept the empty boxes.
And the cardboard
is actually much
sturdier.
- Hey, roomies. I moved
all my stuff back in.
- What stuff?
- Me! I'm my own stuff, baby.
- Well, we're glad you're back.
- And we promise to be more
sensitive to your feelings.
You're not a third wheel.
- The hell I'm not!
Working in a tight-knit
collaborative team
made me realize I hate
being part of a team!
I prefer being a third wheel.
- Good. Because you're
totally a third wheel.
Just pretend
I'm not even here.
Ahh...